Guide to the Boswell Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Additional papers, Series XX
  - RELATED PAPERS
    - Family papers
      - Campbell of Loudoun
        - "Craigend's suit", 1678 (Box 186, Folder 3334)
        - Special retour, 1733 (Box 186, Folder 3335)
        - Teind disposition, 1659 (Box 186, Folder 3336)
          Teind disputes
      - Carr of Etall
        - Genealogical chart, 1795 (Box 187, Folder 3337)
      - Primrose of Rosebery
        - Debt progress, 1709-24, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3338-42)
    - Freeholders
      - Freeholders' Rolls, 1708 (Box 187, Folder 3343)
    - Instructions
      - Royal orders to Sir John Fortescue, 1586 (Box 187, Folder 3344)
    - Memorabilia
      - Beadwork, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3345)
      - "Infant's delight", n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3346)
      - Leather cover, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3347)
      - Notebook, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3348)
      - Painting on wood, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3349)
      - Pocket book, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3350)
      - "Rochester"--signature and seal (Box 187, Folder 3351)
      - Seal of Richard Cromwell (Box 187, Folder 3351)
    - Physician's Guild
      - Legal case, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3352)
    - Printed
      - The A, B, C, with the Shorter Catechism..., 1732 (Box 187, Folder 3353)
      - Act of the Associate Synod..., 1747 (Box 187, Folder 3354)
      - Act, Declaration, and Testimony for the Doctrine..., 1746 (Box 187, Folder 3355)
      - A Defense of the Reformation-- Principles of the Church of Scotland..., 1739 (Box 188, Folder 3356)
        - bound with: Answers by the Associate Presbytery to Reasons of Dissent, 1744 (Box 188, Folder 3356)
      - Erskine, Ralph: A Review of Mr. Gib's Remarks, 1748 (Box 188, Folder 3357)
      - Unidentified fragments, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3358)
    - Proclamation by James VI
      - Recipe book, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3360)
      - Royal warrants, 1715-19, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3361)
      - Scroll submissions of loyalty, 1688 (Box 188, Folder 3362)
      - "Supplicatio ad Papam", n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3363)
      - Writings
        - "Ane meditasione for wakening the secur sowle", n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3364)
        - Notes for an index, probably of a church history (Box 189, Folder 3365)
        - "Universal Politics; or, the Politics of Reason and Good Sense", [ca. 1785?] (Box 189, Folder 3366)
  - OTHER PAPERS
    - Bonds, 1672, 1715, n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3367)
    - Charters, 1680-1730 (Box 189, Folder 3368-75)
    - Contracts, 1681-1709 (Box 189, Folder 3376)
    - Hornings, 1701-19 (Box 189, Folder 3377)
    - Indenture, 1733 (Box 189, Folder 3378)
    - Retours, 1693-1784 (Box 189, Folder 3379-83)
    - Sasines, 1653-1774 (Box 190, Folder 3384-92)
    - Unidentified tack, 1732 (Box 190, Folder 3393)
    - Warrants, 1731, 1771 (Box 190, Folder 3394)
    - Unidentified documents, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3395-99)
    - Unidentified documents, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 4000-02)
    - Wrappers, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 4003-13)
    - Wrappers, n.d. (Box 192, Folder 4014-20)
  - OVERSIZE
    - "Particulars", n.d. (Box 193, Folder 4021)
    - Plans of Estate, n.d. (Box 193, Folder 4022-23)
    - Commission by Mary, Queen of Scots, 1562 (Box 193, Folder 4024)
    - Bonar of Rassy, [15th c?] (Box 193, Folder 4025-26)
    - Campbell, Horne Tooke: charters
      - Campbell, Horne Tooke, 1750 (Box 194, Folder 4027)
      - Campbell, Horne Tooke: Charter, 1792 (Box 194, Folder 4028)
      - Campbell of Loudoun: teinds, 1630-78, n.d. (Box 194, Folder 4029)
      - Seal of Richard Cromwell, 1659 (Box 195, Folder 4030)
      - Charter, ca. 1550 (Box 195, Folder 4031)
      - Wrapper with seal, n.d. (Box 195, Folder 4032)